





Kafeel.ansari@rocketmail.com





KafeelAhamadAnsari

Personal info

C/o.mrSaifuddin Ansari

Mh.Sipah.PoSadar.Distt.Jaunpur (222001) up

Contact.7275831759,8858029999

e-mail-kafeel.iipm786@gmail.com

Objective

Efficiencyto enjoy the challenges of marketing in a reputed organization i can apply my skill and organization skill to achieve organization goal and also help my organization to achieve greater.

Professional profile

My degree is in businessmanagement I also have interest in marketing in terms of customer service market research consumer behavior and brand addressing. my job is as sales and marketing assistant where I had the opportunity to work face to face with customer providing the product. The company had fallowing up on old client and making strategies to pursuit new customer.

Work experience

Marketing manager U.P East (Indicium assessment pvt.ltd)

September 2014 to Nov 2014

- Marketing of I.S.O Certification
- Conduct business plan review meetings with sales team
- Maintain relationship with existing customers for repeat business
- Maintain contacts with processionals and personal contacts to build referrals
- Provide timely feedback to the sales personnel regarding their sales performance

<u>Sales Officer</u>(sunny motors pvt. Ltd.Lucknow)

August 2012 January 2014

- Prepare the customer profile card
- Demonstration of the vehicle to the customer
- Offer the test drive
- Value chain services and end to end sell

- Strong team-building skills
- Reviewed business plans and set goals for future
- Coordinated departments to focus on goal plans.
- Held monthly task completion contests to encourage staff
- Excellent goal tracking and report writing

TSM (Inlead Mobile Pvt Ltd OPPO)

January2021 to Present

- Handing the Area of 1600 Pcs Market
- Strong working on a low Infra site to push our business in good platform
- Promotion activities for new products.
- Executing strategies for market penetration for new products as well as increasing the share of the existing products.
- Deep monitoring of Reports with business Key KPI to complete all task on time.
- Managing Sales Team and Channel Partners and ensuring a Good ROI (Return on Investment).

Technical skill

- Window 97/2000/2007/XP.MS office internet application
- Tally 9.0
- Microsoft Excel

Extra achievement

Certificate of excellence awarded for participating in the (role play competition) at IIPMLucknow campus.

Education

Completed full time programme in small industry interface leading to master in business administration (M.B.A) with specialization in marketing.(M.S University Tamilnadu) IIPM Lucknow June 2010 to May 2012

Name of Graduation degree, 2009

Graduation (B.A) from VBS Purvanchal University Jaunpur UP

Class XII, 2006

Tilakdhari Singh Inter collage jaunpur

Class X, 2004

Arya Inter collage jaunpur